

m: 7863064012 r.madeleine62@yahoo.com 400 W 29TH PL APT 102, HIALEAH, FL 33012

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Organized professional bringing strengths in handling work independently and solving routine problems without oversight. Offers expertise in quality customer service, self motivated with the ability to quickly learn new processes.

Skilled team player with strong background in high paste environments. Works well independently to handle assignments and always ready to go beyond basics assignments. Quick learner with good computer abilities.

Hardworking and focused on completing work quickly to consistently exceed targets. Reliable team member accustomed to taking on challenging tasks. Dedicated to business success.

SKILLS

- Multitasking
- Verbal communication
- · Problem-solving
- Documentation

- Customer relations
- Attention to detail
- Write reports

EXPERIENCE

Security Guard , SMI Security Management Innovations , Jul 2016 - Jul 2017, Doral, FL

- Monitored entrances and exists personally and through the use of CCTV to protect against unauthorized individuals.
- Patrolled the premises to identify and quickly respond to suspicious individuals or activities.
- Completed daily reports outlining regular activities and notable incidents, including theft and property damage.
- Skillfully operated hand-held devices and scanning machinery to complete through checks.
- Managed daily tasks consistently and sought out opportunities to go beyond requirements and support business targets.

Cellphone Production Worker, Cooper General, Oct 2015 - Dec 2016, Doral, FL

- Reviewed the incoming orders and helped with the functioning of device maintaining a demanding schedule.
- Helped managers improve area operations by sharing customer feedback and contributing new ideas.
- Collaborated well with team members to carry out daily assignments and achieve team targets.

Production Worker, Universal Bakery, Jan 2014 - Jul 2014, Opa-locka, FL

- Greeted customers, responded to questions, and offered product and decorating suggestions.
- Maintained high standards for cake decorating and product freshness.
- Inspected bakery products to determine compliance with quality standards, weight specifications, and presentation.
- Operated and maintained all bakery department equipment.

EDUCATION

TCI Institute - Ilialoati, IL

• Vocational School Certificate.

Associate of Arts, Computer & Programming

Siboney Computer Center - Siboney, Havana, Cuba

• Graduated with distinction.

6 1982